freewayinsurance.com 2014-11-27

# Freeway Insurance

You have certain rights under state and federal law with respect to the privacy of information Freeway Insurance Services, Inc., and its Affiliated Companies (collectively “we”, “our” or “us”) obtain about you when we place insurance on your behalf or provide related insurance services primarily for personal, family, or household use.  We will only share your information for purposes of placing your insurance, to offer you products and services, or as otherwise permitted by law.

This Privacy Notice outlines our information sharing practices to help you understand how we protect your privacy, when we collect and use information about you, and the measures we take to safeguard that information.

## **COLLECTION OF INFORMATION**

We collect  **nonpublic personal information**  about you to place insurance on your behalf or provide other products or services.  The categories of  **nonpublic personal information**  that we collect about you are from the following sources:

  * Information we receive from you on applications, forms, and questionnaires, including but not limited to your occupation, current employer, address, birth date, marital status, driver’s license number, social security number, driving record, and health conditions;

  * Information about your transactions with us, our affiliates, or previous insurers, such as your policy coverage, claims information, premiums, and payment history; and

  * Information we receive from third party reporting agencies, such as motor vehicle reports which disclose driving history and credit reporting agencies.

## **INFORMATION WE DISCLOSE**

We may disclose  **nonpublic personal information  **we collect about you, as described above, to Affiliated Companies and nonaffiliated companies that perform insurance, financial, and marketing services on our behalf (and such marketing services may include, without limitation, calling, texting, emailing or sending messages to your land line phone number, cellular phone number or email address regarding products or services, each of which you are hereby consenting to unless you follow the opt-out procedure described below).

## **MEDICAL INFORMATION**

We will not disclose  **medical information**  about you unless allowed by federal or state law or pursuant to your expressed written consent.

## **YOUR CHOICE**

If you prefer that we not share  **nonpublic personal information  **with Affiliated Companies and nonaffiliated companies, except as otherwise permitted by law, you may request an Opt-Out Form by calling toll free, 1-877-790-2425 (please have all of your policy numbers and mailing address available when requesting Opt-Out Forms).  A form will be mailed to your attention.  We will implement your request within a reasonable time after we receive the completed form.  You may opt-out only by completing the Opt-Out Form.

## **CORRECTION OF NONPUBLIC PERSONAL INFORMATION**

You have the right, upon request to us, to access to and reproduction of  **nonpublic personal information**  about you in our possession.  Additionally, you have the right, upon request, to correction, amendment or deletion of such  **nonpublic personal information** , and, if we disagree with your request, to add your views to our records. In order to obtain your information or make such requests you must call the toll-free number above.

## **CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY**

We protect your  **nonpublic personal information**.  Only employees who provide products or services to you will have access to such information.  We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal and state regulations to guard your  **nonpublic personal financial information**.

## **AFFILIATED COMPANIES**

Affiliated Companies mean companies related by common ownership or control, directly or indirectly, with Freeway Insurance Services, Inc.  They can be financial and nonfinancial companies. Our Affiliated Companies include:  Freeway Insurance Services, Inc., Freeway Administrative Services, Inc., Freeway Dealer Services, Inc., SSB Insurance Services, Inc.,  Seguros Sin Barreras Insurance Services, Sacramento Auto Insurance Center, Inc. dba Cost-U-Less Insurance Center, Freeway Insurance Services of Arizona, Inc., Freeway Insurance Services of Nevada, Inc., Vern Fonk Insurance Services, Inc., Auto Insurance Discounters, Inc., Freeway Insurance Services of New Jersey, Inc., Freeway Insurance Services of New York, Inc., Advanced Auto Insurance, Freeway Insurance Services of Florida, Inc., The Keller Group, Inc., CW Baker-Foltz Insurance Agency,  Lewiston Insurance Agency, Coppola Agency, James S. Sullivan Agency, Multi-State Insurance Services, Inc., Multi-State General Agency, Inc., All Star General Insurance Agency LLC,  Stonewood Insurance Services, Inc., Freeway Managing General Agency, Inc. dba Texas State Low Cost, 1-Stop Insurance, and Freeway Insurance Services of Texas, Inc.  Please note that our Affiliated Companies transact business through various DBAs and may change from time to time.  The list of Affiliated Companies above is not intended to be complete.
